stopsmokingcoach.eu 2012-12-03

# i change

**Privacy Policy  
**

****1\. General  
This website is managed by Brand New Day NV (BrandNewDay), with registered offices at Park 51 Site, Persilstraat 51C, bus 301, 3020 Herent, Belgium, entered in the RLP Leuven, company number 0480.270.358.  
BrandNewDay is responsible for the processing of personal information within the meaning of the Act of 8 December 1992 on the protection of privacy with regard to the processing of personal information.  
Personal information is handled with care. For information on the privacy policy and the processing of personal information via this website, including exercising your right to inspection and correction, contact us via the information provided below.  
2\. Consent to process personal information.  
By accessing and using this website and the electronic messages of BrandNewDay, you are expressly agreeing to the content and terms and conditions of this privacy policy. When you visit this website, and when you provide BrandNewDay with personal information, you are giving BrandNewDay your express, written consent to gather, use and process the personal information in accordance with the purposes described below. You have the right to withdraw your consent at any time without specifying a reason..  
3\. What personal information is processed?  
BrandNewDay processes the following details and personal information, among others.  
3.1. Expressly provided information: the information expressly provided by you, such as user name, password, e-mail, sex, age, postal code and level of education, your choice to receive tips, etc. By providing this information, you are giving your express, written consent for it to be processed in accordance with the purposes described below.  
3.2. Automatically gathered information: as well as the information gathered with your express, written consent, information may also be gathered automatically, such as your IP address, your computer's browser type, the operating system and other general information relating to your visit to the website, such as generally measuring the number of visitors, the pages visited, etc.  
3.3. Cookies: during your visit, "cookies" may be placed on your computer's hard drive. Cookies help the website respond more efficiently to the wishes and preferences of our visitors. Accepting cookies is not compulsory. Access to the website is not dependent upon accepting cookies; at any time, you can use your browser's settings to stop cookies from being placed on your hard drive. In principle, your browser allows cookies to be blocked, warnings to be received before cookies are installed or installed cookies to be removed from your hard drive manually or automatically at the end of each browser session. See your Internet browser's instructions for details.  
3.4. Sensitive information: if the processed information contains sensitive personal information, e.g. information about your lifestyle or psychosocial or medical information, then you are giving your express, written consent for the processing of the sensitive information in question via the procedure for signing up or registering new users and also from that point on for further processing, for the purposes described below.  
4\. Purposes of the processing  
The personal information relating to you is processed with a view to allowing the website to function, analysing the visit and the processed information and sending newsletters.  
As a result of taking part in the programme, information is processed with a view to general support, including practical advice (customised tips to change your habits), diaries (recording habits and supporting information in a diary and monthly report), summary charts (to follow the evolution of habits), motivation assessments (to analyse and boost motivation), daily tips (sent via e-mail), mini-tests, a forum, individual answers from experts to questions, and with a view to processing anonymous information for scientific and statistical research purposes.  
Except with your express consent, personal information is not processed with a view to direct marketing. The information is also only processed by contractually-bound third parties, if necessary for the specified purposes, such as to programmers to allow the information technology to function, to service providers for hosting information, to researchers for processing in connection with statistical and scientific purposes, etc.  
5\. Right to access and improvements and changes to the privacy policy.  
You have the right at all times to inspect and correct your personal information. You may submit a request to this effect via the information provided below. Any changes to the privacy policy will be announced via this page. You undertake to check this page regularly.  
6\. Company contact information  
NV Brand New Day  
Park 51 Site  
Persilstraat 51C, bus 301  
3020 Herent - Belgium  
RLP    0480.270.358  
Tel.      +32 (0)16.22.88.93  
E-mail info@brandnewday.eu
